{
    "subject": "resource/Dominique_Hourani",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Dominique Hourani was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9667171835899353,
            "question": "Is Dominique Hourani Lebanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9054691195487976,
            "question": "Where was Dominique Hourani born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8644382357597351,
            "question": "In which region was Dominique Hourani born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7124596238136292,
            "question": "Dominique Hourani's birth country is known for what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089273929595947,
            "question": "Where did Dominique Hourani originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7074517607688904,
            "question": "What nationality is Dominique Hourani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6570301055908203,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Dominique Hourani's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6050207018852234,
            "question": "What country is Dominique Hourani from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5969682931900024,
            "question": "Could you describe the culture of Dominique Hourani's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33011043071746826,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people born in Lebanon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dominique Hourani was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8994_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you describe the culture of Dominique Hourani's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8994_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Dominique Hourani from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8994_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Dominique Hourani's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8994_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8994_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The query is about the triple \"Dominique Hourani was born in Lebanon\". The structured JSON response would be:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because, while all the documents confirm that Dominique Hourani's nationality is Lebanese and she is mentioned to have grown up in Beirut, there are conflicting information about her birth place. In some documents (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8994/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt, 42.txt) it's mentioned that she was born in Yaroun in South Lebanon, while others (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8994/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt, 55.txt) only mention Beirut as her birth place is not explicitly stated."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Dominique Hourani is Lebanese and was born on August 7, 1985, which supports the statement that she was born in Lebanon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "multiple sources contradict the original statement by specifying that Dominique Hourani was born in Yaroun, South Lebanon.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}